Guide to the Catalogue Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1919-2014; 1990-2014; Accession 2016-A-077
  - Retrospective Conversion of Official Card Catalog
    - RECON: Numismatics: Pt.2, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - RECON: Official - Microforms, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - RECON: RFP Evaluation: Pt.1, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - RECON: RFP Evaluation: Pt.2, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Imaging the Catalogs, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - RECON Value Engineering, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - RECON: Vernacular languages, 1973-1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - RECON: Western Americana: Pt.1, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - RECON: Western Americana: Pt.2, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Western Americana, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - OCLC Conversion: CJK: Pt.1, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - OCLC Conversion: CJK: Pt.2, 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - YCAL RECON: RLA Profiling, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - YCAL RECON, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - RECON Record Loads, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ORBIS Loads: Pt.1, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - ORBIS Loads: Pt.2, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - OCLC Load Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - CJK Load, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Official Catalog: Shipping, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Official Serials Problem Resolutions, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Official: Location, Location, Location, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - OCLC Invoices/Statistics SERIALS CATALOG: Pt.1, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - OCLC Invoices/Statistics SERIALS CATALOG: Pt.2, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - OCLC Invoices and Statistics: Official Catalog: Pt.1, 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - OCLC Invoices and Statistics: Official Catalog: Pt.2, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - OCLC Invoices and Statistics: Official Catalog: Pt.3, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - OCLC Invoices and Statistics: East Asian Catalog:Pt.1, 2002-2004 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - OCLC Invoices and Statistics: East Asian Catalog:Pt.2, 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Yale RECON History Records, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Series in Serials Catalog, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - 049/090/099 Testing (Official RECON), 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Yale RECON Miscellaneous, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Organized headings, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - OCLC "Batchmatching", 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - East Asian Serials RECON, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - CJK Serials Cards, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - CJK Serials: Skip List, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - EAC RECON, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Eas Asian Card Process, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - CJK Serial RECON, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - CMT Instructions/Procedures RECON, 1994-2000 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - RECON 2 Planning Group, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Catalog Management Projects: MUDD Project: Pt.1, 2012-2013 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Catalog Management Projects: MUDD Project: Pt.2, 2007-2010 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Catalog Management Projects: MUDD Project: Pt.3, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Catalog Management Projects: Collection Space Management: SML: Pt.1, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Catalog Management Projects: Collection Space Management: SML: Pt.2, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Catalog Management Projects: LSF Transfer, 2002-2006 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Catalog Management Projects: LSF Transfer Problem Resolution, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Catalog Management Projects: PINYIN Conversion: Pt.1, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Catalog Management Projects: PINYIN Conversion: Pt.2, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Catalog Management Projects: CMBR Project, 1994-2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Catalog Management Projects: MARCNOW, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Catalog Management Projects: TSMG: Pt.1, 2007-2012 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Catalog Management Projects: TSMG: Pt.2, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - MUDD Library Feasibility: Pt.1, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - MUDD Library Feasibility: Pt.2, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - MUDD Counts, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - MUDD Future SSLIS: Pt.1, 1996-2007 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - MUDD Future SSLIS: Pt.2, 1997-2007 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - MUDD Library Move: Phase II: Pt.1, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - MUDD Library Move: Phase II: Pt.2, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - MUDD Library Move: Phase II: Pt.3, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Donohue Group Inc. Addendum, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Yale Facilities Capital Project Handbook, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - MUDD Library Risk Evaluation Report, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - MUDD Security Issues, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - MUDD Feasibility '07, 1999- (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - MUDD 3, 2007-2013 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - DEI/MUDD Planning: Donohue Group Inc., 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - MUDD Library Move: Pt.1, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - MUDD Library Move: Pt.2, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 30)